Guide to the Robert Landy Papers MC.259
New York University Archives
Robert Landy Papers
1967-2016
New York University Archives
Landy, Robert J.
MC.259
12.5 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 18 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes
265 Gigabytes in 1,029 computer files
47 sound tape reels
2 videoreels (1/2 inch)
19 videocassettes (vhs)
16 videocassettes (u-matic)
Robert Landy (b. 1944) is professor emeritus at New York University's Drama Therapy Program, playwright, and theatre director. He founded the Drama Therapy Program at New York University (NYU) in 1984. In addition to his tenure at NYU, Landy has over 35 years of clinical experience in drama therapy, working with children and adults. The Robert Landy Papers document Landy's intellectual, professional, and artistic activities in theatre, his scholarly writing on drama therapy, and his work as a professor of drama therapy. The collection dates from 1967 to 2016 and includes paper, born-digital, and audiovisual material. The material in the collection includes draft and published versions of scripts, articles, and books written by Landy and others; analog and digital audio and video recordings of plays and theatrical events directed by Landy; notes and other material related to classes taught by Landy at NYU; and notes, correspondence, and publicity material related to international trainings led by Landy. A large part of the collection documents Landy's work on NYU's Sunrise Semester (1979-1981) and his book God Lives in Glass (2001), which he later adapted for the stage.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions, with the following exceptions.
Repository permission is required for access to materials created by children and used in the creation of God Lives in Glass and City Lights Youth Theatre: Standing Tall. Please contact the University Archives, university-archives@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2641.
Material pertaining to individual student records may be restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Biographical Note
Robert Landy (b. 1944) is professor emeritus at New York University's Drama Therapy Program, playwright, and theatre director. He began teaching at New York University (NYU) in 1979 and founded the university's Drama Therapy Program in 1984. In addition to his tenure at NYU, Landy has over 35 of clinical experience in drama therapy, working with children and adults. In the 1979-1980 academic year, he taught the class "Drama in Education" through NYU's televised distance learning program, Sunrise Semester. Since the 1980s, Landy has led trainings for drama therapy professionals and given lectures on drama therapy throughout the United States and other countries. In addition to his work in drama therapy, Landy is also a theatre director and playwright. Since the late 1960s, he has written and directed his own original works, as well as plays he adapted from the works of Horatio Alger and William Shakespeare. Landy has also written books and scholarly articles on drama, drama therapy, and related topics.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Robert Landy in 2015, with additional accretions in 2016 and 2017. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 15.042, 2016.018, 2016.022, 2016.039, 2017.013, and 2019.042.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in alphabetical order by type of material and in alphabetical order by title within that arrangement. Episodes of Sunrise Semester are arranged in chronological order according to the schedule listed in the course outline.
Material that consists of a large amount of paper material or any audiovisual material is listed under its full title. The inventory lists box and folder numbers for an alphabetical range of titles for other material.
Scope and Contents
The Robert Landy Papers document Landy's work in theatre and education between 1967 and 2016. The collection includes paper, born-digital, and audiovisual material documenting his professional and artistic activities in theatre, his work as a professor of drama therapy, and his scholarly writing on drama therapy. Material in the collection includes draft and published scripts, articles, and books written by Landy and others; audio recordings of plays and theatrical events directed by Landy; material related to classes taught by Landy at NYU; and material related to trainings in drama therapy led by Landy in the United States (US), Europe, and Asia. The bulk of the collection documents, "Drama in Education", Landy's class taught through NYU's television program Sunrise Semester (1979-1981); his files on classes taught through NYU's Drama Therapy program in the 2000s; and his book God Lives in Glass (2001), which he later adapted for the stage. The God Lives in Glass paper material includes original artwork by children, forms used during interviews with the children, drafts of the book and play. There are also audio recordings of the play God Lives in Glass and scanned copies of notes and forms used by Landy in the course of his research for the book. Landy's work as a playwright and theatre director is documented though published and draft scripts, notes, photographs, audio recordings of performances, and publicity materials for plays. The scripts include original compositions by Landy and plays adapted by Landy from works by Horatio Alger and William Shakespeare. Included in this material is original correspondence on which Letters from Sing Sing was based, including correspondence between Landy and the man on whom the character of Michael is based.
Material documenting Landy's career as an educator, dates from the late 1970s through the mid 2010s, and includes class outlines, syllabi, notes for lectures, copies of readings for class discussions, and correspondence and awards celebrating Landy's achievements as a professor. This also includes video and audio recordings of "Drama in Education", a class taught by Landy during the academic year of 1979-1980 for NYU's television program Sunrise Semester, as well as paper course outlines, notes, and study guides for the classes. Also included is material documenting Landy's work as a lecturer on drama therapy at National Association for Drama Therapy conferences, and as a trainer leading seminars and workshops on drama therapy. This material dates from the mid 1990s through the mid 2010s, and includes correspondence regarding planning of events, printed publicity materials, video recordings of trainings, and documentation on methods taught at the trainings.
Other material in the collection includes correspondence with colleagues, some files include publications by correspondents and notes by Landy; clippings and publications with articles by and about Landy; and issues of Arts in Psychotherapy, a scholarly journal edited by Landy in the 1990s.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact the University Archives (university-archives@nyu.edu) with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted.
An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Children -- Religious life.; Drama -- Therapeutic use.; American drama -- 20th century.; Distance education.; New York University -- Faculty; Steinhardt School of Education. Drama Therapy Program.
- Conferences, 1984-2012; cuid5197 (Box 9, Folder 1-12)
- Correspondence, 1970-2010; cuid5196 (Box 8, Folder 8-15, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_2)
- Music and photography, 1978-2010; cuid5213 (Box 13, Folder 40-42, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_3)
- Teaching -- Ad, 1999-2014; cuid5203 (Box 11, Folder 1-7, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_5)
- Teaching -- Albert Cullum, Undated; cuid5130; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5130)
- Teaching -- City Lights Youth Theatre: Standing Tall, 2001-2002; cuid5204 (Box 11, Folder 8-10)
- Teaching -- City Lights Youth Theatre: Standing Tall -- Children's writings, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 6-8)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Repository permission is required for access to materials created by children and used in the creation of City Lights Youth Theatre: Standing Tall. Please contact the University Archives, university-archives@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2641.
- Teaching -- Cl - Co, 1972-1995; cuid5205 (Box 11, Folder 11, Box 12, Folder 1-2, Box 23, Folder 1)
- Teaching -- Dialogue with Sue Jennings, 1992-2015; cuid5124; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5124a-c, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_10)
- Teaching -- Dis, 2002; cuid5206 (Box 12, Folder 3, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_7)
- Teaching -- Drama Therapy f - Group D, 1988-2016; cuid5207 (Box 12, Folder 4-8, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_12)
- Teaching -- Drama Therapy, Undated; cuid5184; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original container is labeled: Drama Therapy. (Box 22, Cassette MC.259.cuid5184)
- Teaching -- Faculty Series on University Living, 2016 (Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_13)
- Teaching -- Group Thesis Project, 1994; cuid5125; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5125, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_14)
- Teaching -- I - P, 1984-2015; cuid5208 (Box 12, Folder 9-13)
- Teaching -- Role Method, 2000-2016; cuid5127; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5127, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_16)
  Scope and Contents
  Label reads: R. Landy + 1st yr class role method
- Teaching -- Role Theory and Role Method in Drama Therapy, 2016; cuid5209 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Teaching -- Role Therapy, 2005; cuid5128; 0 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 18, Cassette MC.259.cuid5128)
- Teaching -- Sh - St, 1994-2015; cuid5210 (Box 12, Folder 15-18, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_17)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama in Education, 1979-1980; cuid5211 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Overview of the Course, 1979; cuid5135; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5135)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Definitions and Issues in Drama in Education, 1979; cuid5136; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5136, Box 13, Folder 9)
  The guest is Lowell Swortzell.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- A History of America Drama and Theatre, 1979; cuid5137; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5137, Box 13, Folder 10)
  The guest is Nellie McCaslin.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama as Process #1: Getting Started, 1979; cuid5138; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original container is labeled: SS-4, SS Sik + Kids. (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5138a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5138b, Box 13, Folder 11)
  The guest is Geraldine Brain Siks.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama as Process #2: Getting Started (continued), 1979; cuid5139; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) Original containers are labeled: Sunrise Semester Air Master Air: Sept 26 1979 "Getting Started Continued - Part Two" Eps. #5; and SS Sik + kids SS-6. (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5139a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5139b, Cassette MC.259.cuid5139c, Box 13, Folder 12)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama as Process #3: Story Dramatization, 1979; cuid5140; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original container is labeled: TV Clock Coleman Jennings EPS. #6. (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5140a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5140b, Box 13, Folder 13)
  The guest is Coleman Jennings.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama as Process #4: The Child as Playmaker, 1979; cuid5142; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) Original containers are labeled: SS- Korty SS-7; SS- Korty SS-8; and SS- Korty SS-9. (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5142a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5142b-d)
  The guest is Carol Korty.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Children Talk about Drama, 1979; cuid5141; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Cassette is labeled "Children Talk About Drama. Intro: "This morning we have an interesting panel of guests." Original container is labeled SS Landy + Kids #11. (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5141a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5141b)
  Guests include students of Rob Lesser and the 92nd St. Y.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama as Process #6: Drama in an Inner City School, 1979; cuid5143; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5143, Box 13, Folder 14)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama as Process #7: Improvisation, 1979; cuid5145; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5145, Box 13, Folder 15)
  The guest is John Hodgson.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama as Process #8: Simulation, 1979; cuid5144; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5144, Box 13, Folder 16)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama as Process #9: An Interview with Gavin Bolton, 1979; cuid5146; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original cassette is labeled: Sunrise Semester Mr. Gavin Bolton. (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5146a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5146b, Box 13, Folder 17)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Teaching History through Drama #1, 1979; cuid5147; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5147, Box 13, Folder 18)
  The guest is Nancy Swortzell.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Teaching History through Drama #2, 1979; cuid5148; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5148, Box 13, Folder 19)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Teaching Language Arts through Drama, 1979; cuid5149; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5149, Box 13, Folder 20)
  The guest is James Moffett.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Teaching Writing through Drama, 1979; cuid5150; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5150)
  Guests include Linda Balsam and Joan Kaufman.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Teaching Reading through Drama, 1979; cuid5151; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5151, Box 13, Folder 21)
  The guest is Shirlee Sloyer.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Theatre-in-Education: Principles and Practices, 1979; cuid5152; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5152, Box 13, Folder 22)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Theatre-in-Education: Practical Application in Schools, 1979; cuid5153; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 19, Reel MC.259.cuid5153)
  Guests include Lynda Zimmerman and members of the Creative Arts Team at New York University.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Theatre-in-Education: Practical Application in Schools, 1979; cuid5154; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5154, Box 13, Folder 23)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Children Perform the Classics, 1979; cuid5155; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original cassette is labeled: Uncle Vanya SS #5. (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5155a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5155b, Box 12, Folder 19, Box 13, Folder 24)
  Guests include Phil Lopate, Lisa Cowen, and Angus Johnston.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- School Drama as Product: The School Play, 1979; cuid5156; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5156, Box 13, Folder 25)
  Guests include Joan Johnston and Michael Tempel.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama in the Community, 1979; cuid5157; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original cassette is labeled: #3 Prof Richard Courtney. (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5157a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5157b, Box 13, Folder 26)
  The guest is Richard Courtney.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- The Museum as a Source of Drama Education, 1979; cuid5158; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5158, Box 13, Folder 27)
  The guest is Tom Cahill.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Training Counselors through Improvisation, 1979; cuid5159; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5159, Box 13, Folder 28)
  Guests include Joyce St. George and Francis P. Canavan.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Exploring Concerns of Teenagers through Drama, 1979; cuid5160; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5160)
  Guests include Edward Welch and three students.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Sociodrama and Psychodrama in the Community, 1979; cuid5161; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5161)
  The guest is James Sacks.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama/Theatre for the Handicapped, 1979; cuid5162; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5162, Box 13, Folder 29)
  The guests are Karen [Luxton?], Jane [Frannila?], and Elliot Schloss.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Puppetry for/with the Mentally Retarded, 1979; cuid5163; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5163)
  The guest is Lea Wallace.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama and Therapy, 1979; cuid5172; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5172)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama for/with Emotionally Disturbed Individuals, 1979; cuid5165; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original container is labeled: CBS-TV Sunrise Semester November 30, 1979 Drama in Education: Drama Therapy with Gertrude Schattner. (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5165a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5165b, Box 13, Folder 30)
  The guest is Gertrud Schattner.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama/Theatre for/with the Blind, 1979; cuid5166; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5166, Box 13, Folder 31)
  The guest is Rick Curry.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama/Theatre for/with the Orthopedically Handicapped, 1979; cuid5167; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5167)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama/Theatre for/with the Elderly, 1979; cuid5168; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5168, Box 13, Folder 32)
  Guests include Bonnie Robbins and Paula Gray.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama/Theatre in the Deaf Community, 1979; cuid5169; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5169, Box 13, Folder 33)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama/Theatre in the Black Community, 1979; cuid5170; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5170)
  Guests include Ellen Cleghorne and members of The Family.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Drama/Theatre in the Black and Hispanic Communities, 1979; cuid5171; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5171, Box 13, Folder 34)
  Guests include Marvin Felix Camillo and Rose Calavido.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Theatre for Children #1: The Playwright, 1979; cuid5173; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5173, Box 13, Folder 35)
  The guest is Aurand Harris.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Theatre for Children #2: The Producer/Director, 1979; cuid5164; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original cassette is labeled John Clark Donahue SS #10. (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5164a, Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5164b, Box 13, Folder 36)
  The guest is John Clark Donahue.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Theatre for Children #3: The Actors, 1979; cuid5174; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5174, Box 13, Folder 37)
  Guests include Judith Martin and Irving Burton.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Puppetry in Education, 1979; cuid5175; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5175, Box 13, Folder 38)
  The guest is Maurice Stewart.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Puppetry, Mask, Mime, Myth, 1979; cuid5176; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5176)
  The guest is Tom Miller.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Process Drama and Theatre Reviewed, 1979; cuid5177; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5177, Box 13, Folder 39)
  The guest is Brian Way.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Career Opportunities in Educational Drama, 1979; cuid5178; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5178)
  Guests include Lowell Swortzell and Vera Mowry.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Future Directions: A Preview of Things to Come, 1979; cuid5179; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5179)
  Guests include Ann Shaw and Nellie McCaslin.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Summary and Conclusions, 1979; cuid5180; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5180)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Untitled, 1981; cuid5181; 1 sound tape reels in 1 1/4" sound reel (Box 20, Reel MC.259.cuid5181)
  Labeling on original package reads: Sunrise Semester Drama M26 dubbed 6-3-81.
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Untitled, 1979; cuid5182; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original container labeled: Ep. # H-15 Richard W. Hull. (Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5182)
- Teaching -- Sunrise Semester -- Untitled, 1979; cuid5183; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Original container is labeled: Sunrise Semester H-14. (Box 21, Cassette MC.259.cuid5183)
- Teaching -- T - V, 1983-2015; cuid5212 (Box 13, Folder 1-8, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_18)
- Theatre -- A - K, 1971-2001; cuid5188 (Box 1, Folder 1-14, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_15)
- Theatre -- Letters from Sing Sing, 1994-2010; cuid5189 (Box 2, Folder 1-9, Box 3, Folder 1, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_1)
- Theatre -- Lo - Padrone, 1972-2015; cuid5190 (Box 3, Folder 2-15, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_9, Box Shared University Archives 050, Folder 7)
- Theatre -- Padrone - Ph, 1978-1980; cuid5191 (Box 4, Folder 1-7)
- Theatre -- Rags to Riches, 1975; cuid5185; 1 videoreels (1/2 inch) Original reel is labeled: Rags to Riches rough draft. (Box 22, Reel MC.259.cuid5185, Box 4, Folder 8-9, Box 23, Folder 4-7)
- Theatre -- S - Y, 1969-1983; cuid5192 (Box 4, Folder 10-19, Box 23, Folder 2-3)
- Trainings -- A - Da, 1996-2011; cuid5198 (Box 9, Folder 13-15, Box Electronic Records, E-records UA_MC_259_ER_11)